Ashley Kanas

UX/UI designer

Contact

(845) 370 2214
kanasashleyui@gmail.c
om
Portfolio Website (click)
LinkedIn profile (click)

Education

CareerFoundry, UI
Design Course
Jan 2024 - Nov 2024
Certificates

Skills

- User research
- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- Branding
- Visual design
- Lean UX
- Mockups
- Animation
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- · Attention to detail
- Communication
- Researching
- Empathy
- Time management
- Problem-solving

Tools

- Figma
- GitHub
- Visual Code Studio

Summary

UI designer passionate about design with great communication and time management skills. Specializes in visual design/branding and has a foundational understanding of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

Projects

Crave Restaurant finding responsive web app

March 2024 - July 2024

 Designed high-fidelity mockups and a prototype for a location-based restaurant-finding web app for younger users, based on user interviews and research

Remi | Productivity native app

July 2024 - August 2024

 Curated high-fidelity mockups and prototypes for a motivational productivity app in dark mode, adhering to iOS and Android guidelines

Work experience

Volunteer Bible educator

2014 - present

- Schedules and conducts Bible studies to help students understand and apply what they learn
- Searches for interested individuals through door-to-door visits, phone calls, and letter writing
- Maintains records of those interested
- Prepares discussion outlines and conducts research to support studies
- Works in teams of two during study sessions
- Communicates with students in person, virtually, and by phone
- Uses questions and active listening to understand students' feelings and perspectives
- · Helps students reason and address their needs
- Assists students in discovering concepts that benefit their daily lives
- · Regularly attends meetings to improve teaching skills
- Manages time to be prepared and punctual for study sessions

Freelance baker

2022 - present

- Make and delivered customer orders on time for their event
- Experienced in making cakes, yeasted doughs, laminated pastry, choux pastry, tarts, pies, and custards
- Specializes in presentation and decorating
- Satisfies customers expressed expectations